<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://nbkyn-parks-community.github.io/blog</id>
    <title>nbkyn-parks-community Blog</title>
    <updated>2022-03-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://nbkyn-parks-community.github.io/blog"/>
    <subtitle>nbkyn-parks-community Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://nbkyn-parks-community.github.io/https://nbkparks.org/wp-content/themes/NBKPA-wp_v2.8.7/favicon/favicon-32x32.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Garden Day Planning Session 3/2/2022]]></title>
        <id>Open-Garden-Day-Planning Session-3-2-2022</id>
        <link href="https://nbkyn-parks-community.github.io/blog/Open-Garden-Day-Planning Session-3-2-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[---]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<hr><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="hi-all">Hi all,<a class="hash-link" href="#hi-all" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>Thanks to everyone who tuned in before! So great to hear your ideas for Open Garden Day 2022 (Sat. June 4th) - especially ways to support each other's gardens in North Brooklyn and ways to welcome neighbors into the gardens! </p><p><a href="/blog/notes-3-2-2022">Attached are the notes from the discussion</a>. And below is a recap of the next steps! Please feel free to chime in if anything is missing.</p><p>The next planning meeting is Tues. 4/5 from 6:30-8:00pm. Zoom link below! (And apologies for the confusion with the Zoom link - I've set the same link we used for future meetings going forward.)</p><p>Thanks all,
K.C.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="next-steps">Next Steps:<a class="hash-link" href="#next-steps" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>K.C.: Check in with the DOT about the idea of a map of all of the gardens for a future self-guided tour, in addition to the map for Open Garden Day 2022 specifically</p><p>K.C. &amp; Participating Gardens: Finalize the stops and bike route by <code>Tues. 3/15 to solidify with the DOT </code></p><p>Aim to have fewer formal stops and focus on connecting the gardens overall</p><p>Check in about indicating public restrooms and Citibike stops on the map</p><p>Reps from Powers Street &amp; Red Shed Garden: Discuss the idea of a final event to conclude the route and see what members are interested in, access to power / bathrooms, etc.</p><code>Participating Gardens: By Fri. 4/1</code>, each garden participating in Open Garden Day 2022 should send in a short description and a couple of photos to K.C. and Sam (for print flyers about how to join the gardens and for Sam to add to the website)<code> Participating Gardens: By Fri. 4/29</code>, each garden could aim to send K.C. and Sam more details about activities for Open Garden Day, in order to promote over social media etc.<ul><li>Sam is interested in helping to create sample social media posts</li><li>Ariel to check in with her husband about creating a graphic / flyer for 2022 Open Garden Day in North Brooklyn</li><li>K.C.: Follow up with NBPA to see if they are interested in doing video / social media profiles of gardens</li><li>Mary and Stephen are interested in thinking about donations from local businesses (ex. Snacks, giveaways, t-shirts / safety vests, etc.)</li><li>David is interested in reaching out to local bike shops to see if any of them would be interested in offering free bike repairs, etc. for the bike tour</li><li>Kathy mentioned that Transportation Alternatives could offer free bike lights</li></ul><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="to-discuss">To Discuss:<a class="hash-link" href="#to-discuss" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><ul><li>Bike Rack</li><li>Creating Facebook event</li><li>Creating “Passport” for kids / participants between gardens</li></ul><p>Reaching out to local press</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>K.C. Alvey</name>
        </author>
        <category label="open-garden-day" term="open-garden-day"/>
        <category label="bike" term="bike"/>
        <category label="community" term="community"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes Session 3/2/2022]]></title>
        <id>notes-3-2-2022</id>
        <link href="https://nbkyn-parks-community.github.io/blog/notes-3-2-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NBK Open Garden Day Planning]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>NBK Open Garden Day Planning
3/1/22, 6:30-8:00pm
Zoom Meeting</strong></p><p><strong>Attendees:</strong> Lisa Bloodgood (La Casita Verde), Sam Witke(Powers Street Garden, Olive Street
Garden, Red Shed Garden), Ariel Willmott (Red Shed Garden), Stephen Lewis (Red Shed
Garden, Friends of Cooper Park), John Rauchenberger (Northside Community Garden), David
Najarro (Red Shed Garden), Kathy Park Price (Transportation Alternatives), Mary Witke
(Powers Street Garden, Olive Street Garden, Red Shed Garden), McDavid Moore, Katie
Levinson (Green Dome), Lori Vroegindewey (61 Franklin Street Garden), Edda Figueroa (El
Puente: Espiritu Tierra Community Garden), K.C. Alvey (NYC Parks GreenThumb)</p><p><strong>Agenda Items:</strong>
● Go-around (or put in the chat): What are you hoping to see for Open Garden Day in
North Brooklyn? What’s your vision for the day?
○ David (Red Shed Garden) - having people get together and learn more about the
different gardens
○ Lori (61 Franklin Street Garden) - first public event since COVID, haven’t had first
member meeting yet and we’ll talk about it then; want it to be a joyous occasion
with food, activities for a wide age range, a stop along the bike tour, participate in
the oral history project
○ Lisa Bloodgood (La Casita Verde) - COVID was hard on our garden so having a
chance to celebrate the space, help welcome people into the garden, have fun
and meet our neighbors
○ Katie Levinson (Green Dome) - COVID was also tough for our garden, we always
have people walk into our garden, so having a dedicated day for people to come
see the space
○ Stephen Lewis (Red Shed Garden, Friends of Cooper Park) - seeing the road,
more of my neighborhood
○ John Rauchenberger (Northside Community Garden) - energize people and
welcome people back into the gardens
○ Sam Witke (Powers Street Garden, Olive Street Garden, Red Shed Garden)
○ Ariel Willmott (Red Shed Garden) - excited to be on-site and welcome people into
the garden
○ Mary Witke (Powers Street Garden, Olive Street Garden, Red Shed Garden) -
excited to support the bike tour
○ Kathy Park Price (Transportation Alternatives) - looking forward to checking out
more of the gardens in North Brooklyn
● Updates on bike tour logistics
○ <strong>Open Garden Day NYC is Saturday 6/4</strong> ; overall timefor Open Garden Day
NYC to be determined but flexible to accommodate different types of events
throughout the day
<strong>○ Rain date - Sunday 6/</strong>
○ Recap updates from the DOT, Citibike, Transportation Alternatives (K.C.)</p><p>■ Transportation Alternatives Marshal Guide
■ DOT is happy to put together print / pdf maps of the bike tour and give
feedback on the route safety again, like they did in 2021
● Example ofsign-up formandmapfor the Eastern BrooklynBike
Tour that was in May 2021 from 1-5pm on a Saturday afternoon
for a total of 5.2 miles and 9 stops.
■ Lisa’s question about having a map of the route for the day and a
self-guided map of all the gardens for future reference → <strong>can the DOT
help us with this? Especially if it included the open hours and social
media info</strong>
■ Citibike is offering free discount codes for bikes; just need to dock every
two hours to extend the free rental
■ North Brooklyn Activist Committee of TA would be the main partner - Juan
and Kevin as co-chairs and volunteers
○ Review / discussproposed route(~6-7 miles total);
■ Idea of having some gardens give tours of their spaces and others along
the route that we point out as we bike past; trying to balance overall
length / accessibility and giving a good introduction to the different
community gardens in North Brooklyn
■ Proposed stops ( <strong>bold</strong> means that these gardens havesigned up via the
form or expressed interest already)
● <strong>Green Dome</strong> - starting point
● <strong>61 Franklin St.</strong> - stop / pass by
● Java Street Garden - stop
● Bike alongBrooklyn Greenway, past Bushwick InletPark and
Domino Park
● Berry Street Garden - pass by
● El Puente: Espiritu Tierra Community Garden - stop
● <strong>La Casita Verde</strong> - stop
● Ten Eyck Garden - pass by
● <strong>Sunshine Community Garden</strong> - stop
● <strong>Powers Street Garden</strong> - stop
● Olive Street Garden - pass by
● <strong>Red Shed Garden</strong> - final stop? (or Lentol Garden, anothermile?)
■ Feedback on the route:
● David: Length seems reasonable overall
● John: Could alter the route to pass by Northside Community
Garden
● Lisa: Could use the furthest most gardens as the stopping points
and 1-2 other gardens throughout; could cover the whole route;
idea of noisemakers for bikers
● Stephen: Could we include Friends of Cooper Park’s native
pollinator garden? We have a lot of space where people could
gather</p><p>● Lisa: Similarly, adding McCarren Park Demonstration Garden and
the Manhattan Avenue Street End Park, both friends of groups
that are caring for park spaces and have pollinator gardens
● *<strong>*Could aim to have fewer formal stops on the route and aim
to connect as many of the gardens as possible, that we pass
by
● </strong>Could note where there are public restrooms on the map
(Cooper Park has restrooms), Citibike stops, etc.
● <strong>Need to finalize the route by mid-March to solidify the route
with the DOT (3/15)</strong>
○ Discuss final stop idea
■ People liked this idea - final event at the destination point
■ Stephen: Red Shed Garden has a portapotty but no power and the
reverse for Powers Street Garden
■ Ariel: We’re planning multiple activities at Red Shed Garden - cyanotypes,
food, seed related thing, etc. so we’d be happy to host a final event; I
don’t know in terms of clusters of gardens; we don’t necessarily need a
generator
■ David: We could also build a muffler box around a generator so that the
sound isn’t so bad
■ Stephen: Could consider renting a portapotty for Powers Street Garden if
needed as well
■ Lisa: Could check to see if there’s a business nearby that would be open
to having people use the restroom by Powers Street Garden
<strong>■ </strong>Garden groups at Powers Street and Red Shed to discuss idea of a
final event as the destination and to see what makes sense;<strong> both
gardens towards the end of the proposed route anyway
○ Discuss website(Samuel Witke)
■ Interactive website with virtual tour of the gardens - map, info, etc.
■ Sample from 2019 North Brooklyn Open Garden Day
■ Could still feature all of the gardens that want to participate in the day,
regardless of whether they’re on the bike tour itself
■ Sam can start sharing a new link when this is hosted on a new community
page instead of his personal page - goal of getting more information out
there about your gardens, useful beyond this one event
■ Everyone can have access to make changes or tell Sam what edits are
needed
■ Could also just send Sam the text description for your gardens
■ Goal of an interactive map where you can see the route
</strong>■ <strong>Would just need a short description and photos of each
participating garden → could aim to have this by April 1st
■ </strong>By April 30th, could aim to have more details about on-site
activities for Open Garden Day**</p><p>● Updates on event ideas for individual gardens</p><p>○ OpenGardenDay2022Form Data Samuel Witke
○ Event registration deadline
● Discuss outreach and promotion
○ Social media?
■ Eventbrite/Facebook event
● GreenThumb can help create Eventbrite sign-up links again
● Didn’t get a chance to talk about a Facebook event - pick up on
this for next time
■ Digital assets - save the date, digital map graphic
● Idea of doing social media posts on the same day - posting digital
flyers, etc. on each of the gardens’ social media pages
● Could create sample posts
● Idea of a graphic that’s a nice illustration that could be shared -
Ariel’s husband had expressed interest in helping with this
● Could have a stylized map that the gardens could take it and run
with for social media posts for their own gardens
● Could link to a QR code too so if there are updates, it’s easier
<strong>○ </strong>Sam is interested in helping with social media posts<strong>
■ Videos
● North Brooklyn Parks Alliancehas created video profilesof
gardens, including some GreenThumb gardens, with theAsk a
Gardener series
</strong>● <strong>Could follow up with NBPA to see if they’re interested in
profiling gardens</strong>
○ Flyers
■ GT has template flyers for individual gardens and Community Boards of
gardens - on how to join gardens generally; *<strong>*Couldcreate flyers for
individual gardens to distribute to attendees of Open Garden Day
with info about how to get involved</strong>
● K.C. is happy to help with garden groups on creating these; main
thing is to have description of garden and a couple of photos
<strong>■ </strong>Could do a print / digital flyer for Open Garden Day specifically -
Ariel’s husband may be interested<strong> → the print flyercould be drawn
from the digital flyer (or the other way around)
</strong>● <strong>Could share sample flyers from previous years</strong>
○ T-shirts? Or safety vests?</p><div class="codeBlockContainer_I0IT theme-code-block"><div class="codeBlockContent_wNvx"><pre tabindex="0" class="prism-code language-text codeBlock_jd64 thin-scrollbar" style="color:#393A34;background-color:#f6f8fa"><code class="codeBlockLines_mRuA"><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">■ **Mary is interested in thinking more about what this could look like</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">○ “Passport”?</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">■ Didn’t get a chance to talk about this - pick up on this for next time</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">○ Outreach to additional partners?</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">■ For donations?</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● **Mary and Stephen are interested in thinking more about</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">what this could look like - potential outreach to local</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">businesses for snacks or giveaways</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● **David Najarro is interested in reaching out to local bike</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">shops - to see if any of them would be up for helping with</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">bike repair</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● **Kathy mentioned that Transportation Alternatives could</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">give out free bike lights</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">■ Promotion?</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">○ Local press</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">■ Didn’t get a chance to discuss - pick up on this for next time</span><br></span></code></pre><button type="button" aria-label="Copy code to clipboard" class="copyButton_wuS7 clean-btn">Copy</button></div></div><p>*<strong>*Tuesday 4/5 at 6:30pm → next Zoom meeting</strong></p><p><strong>Next Steps:</strong></p><div class="codeBlockContainer_I0IT theme-code-block"><div class="codeBlockContent_wNvx"><pre tabindex="0" class="prism-code language-text codeBlock_jd64 thin-scrollbar" style="color:#393A34;background-color:#f6f8fa"><code class="codeBlockLines_mRuA"><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● K.C.: Check in with the DOT about the idea of a mapof all of the gardens for a future</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">self-guided tour, in addition to the map for Open Garden Day 2022 specifically</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● K.C. &amp; Participating Gardens: Finalize the stops andbike route by Tues. 3/15 to</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">solidify with the DOT</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">○ Aim to have fewer formal stops and focus on connecting the gardens overall</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">○ Check in about indicating public restrooms and Citibike stops on the map</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Reps from Powers Street &amp; Red Shed Garden: Discussthe idea of a final event to</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">conclude the route and see what members are interested in, access to power /</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">bathrooms, etc.</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Participating Gardens:By Fri. 4/1 , each garden shouldsend in a short description and</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">a couple of photos to K.C. and Sam (for print flyers about how to join the gardens and for</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">Sam to add to the website)</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Participating Gardens:By Fri. 4/29 , each garden couldaim to send K.C. and Sam</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">more details about activities for Open Garden Day, in order to promote over social media</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">etc.</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Sam is interested in helping to create sample socialmedia posts</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Ariel to check in with her husband about creatinga graphic / flyer for 2022 Open Garden</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">Day in North Brooklyn</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● K.C.: Follow up with NBPA to see if they are interestedin doing video / social media</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">profiles of gardens</span><br></span></code></pre><button type="button" aria-label="Copy code to clipboard" class="copyButton_wuS7 clean-btn">Copy</button></div></div><div class="codeBlockContainer_I0IT theme-code-block"><div class="codeBlockContent_wNvx"><pre tabindex="0" class="prism-code language-text codeBlock_jd64 thin-scrollbar" style="color:#393A34;background-color:#f6f8fa"><code class="codeBlockLines_mRuA"><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Mary and Stephen are interested in thinking about donations from local businesses (ex.</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">Snacks, giveaways, t-shirts / safety vests, etc.)</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● David is interested in reaching out to local bikeshops to see if any of them would be</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">interested in offering free bike repairs, etc. for the bike tour</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Kathy mentioned that Transportation Alternatives couldoffer free bike lights</span><br></span></code></pre><button type="button" aria-label="Copy code to clipboard" class="copyButton_wuS7 clean-btn">Copy</button></div></div><p><strong>Bike Rack - To Discuss:</strong></p><div class="codeBlockContainer_I0IT theme-code-block"><div class="codeBlockContent_wNvx"><pre tabindex="0" class="prism-code language-text codeBlock_jd64 thin-scrollbar" style="color:#393A34;background-color:#f6f8fa"><code class="codeBlockLines_mRuA"><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Creating Facebook event</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Creating “Passport” for kids / participants between gardens</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">● Reaching out to local press</span><br></span></code></pre><button type="button" aria-label="Copy code to clipboard" class="copyButton_wuS7 clean-btn">Copy</button></div></div><p><strong>Zoom Link:</strong></p><p>NYC Parks GreenThumb is inviting you to a scheduled Zoom meeting.</p><p>Topic: North Brooklyn Gardener Zoom - Open Garden Day planning
Time: Mar 1, 2022 06:30 PM Eastern Time (US and Canada)</p><p>Join Zoom Meeting
<a href="https://us02web.zoom.us/j/81429077756?pwd=b0lkUEVLL1k2VmhpMDh2YWVOYWV5Zz" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://us02web.zoom.us/j/81429077756?pwd=b0lkUEVLL1k2VmhpMDh2YWVOYWV5Zz</a></p><p>Meeting ID: 814 2907 7756
Passcode: 759381
One tap mobile
+19292056099,,81429077756#,,,,<em>759381# US (New York)
+13017158592,,81429077756#,,,,</em>759381# US (Washington DC)</p><p>Dial by your location
+1 929 205 6099 US (New York)
+1 301 715 8592 US (Washington DC)
+1 312 626 6799 US (Chicago)
+1 346 248 7799 US (Houston)
+1 669 900 6833 US (San Jose)
+1 253 215 8782 US (Tacoma)
Meeting ID: 814 2907 7756
Passcode: 759381
Find your local number: <a href="https://us02web.zoom.us/u/kdSCdEcRyc" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://us02web.zoom.us/u/kdSCdEcRyc</a></p><p>Sample poster from a past event that BQLT had:</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>K.C. Alvey</name>
        </author>
        <category label="open-garden-day" term="open-garden-day"/>
        <category label="bike" term="bike"/>
        <category label="community" term="community"/>
    </entry>
</feed>